Guide to the Stanford University, School of Engineering, Honors Theses SC4-3025
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, School of Engineering, honors theses
1991-2012
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. School of Engineering
SC4-3025
0.75 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University School of Engineering.
Acquisition Information
Theses were transferred to the Stanford Unversity Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011, 2017.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University School of Engineering.
Access to Collection
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Engineering -- Study and teaching.; Student papers.; Stanford University. School of Engineering; Stanford University. School of Engineering; Stanford University. School of Engineering
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Senatore, Michelle, Synthesis, characterization, and OTFT performance of functionalized pentacene derivatives., 2007 (Box 1)
  - Shrestha, Roshan, In-vivo expression of biotin-tagged human Beta-2 adrenergic receptor as a control for in-vitro synthesis and folding., 2005 (Box 1)
  - Pickering, Natalie, Appropriate technology: appropriate for whom? An analysis of a technical training program for rural Sri Lankan women., 1991 (Box 1)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2017-298
  - Ashe, Katy. Baseline Study of Water Quality in the Tambopata River in Southeaster Peru, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Cantu, Jordan Alvarado. Characterizing the fracture toughness behavior and failure mechanisms of PHBV-based composites with stress concentrations for structural applications, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Clarke, Anthony J. Sustainable Innovation Diffusion in the Building Industry: Barriers and Potential Interventions, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Stanford, Madison. Investigation of Murine Models of Anterior Ischemic Optic Neuropathy, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Price-Wright, Erin. Information Cities: Network Optimization and Multi-Dimentional Urban Design, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Miller, Eric. Selective Solution Shearing Deposition of Organic Semiconductor Thin Films, 2012 (Box 1)
  - Liptsey-Rahe, Alexandra. Tenure Formalization in South African Informal Settlements: Mechanisms and Nuances of Urban Upgrading throught Title Deed Delivery, 2011 (Box 1)
  - Lee, Diana Yiyng. Microkinetic Modeling of the Electroreduction of Carbon Dioxide on a Copper Catalyst (Box 1)
  - Essig, Chiara. Assessing Energy Efficiency in Japan's Manufacturing Sector, 2012 (Box 1)